Coffee.
咖啡
-Thank you. -Cappuccino.
-谢谢 -卡布其诺
And a nice,hot cider for Monica.
摩妮卡的热苹果酒
Thank you.
谢谢
Rach,why does my cinnamon stick have an eraser?
瑞秋,为何我的肉桂棒上有橡皮擦?
That's why.
这就是原因,
Sorry.
对不起
The One With The Stoned Guy
六人行 第1季 第15集 大麻客
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 荣誉出品 河马根据网络字幕微调制作
Chandler?
钱德
Miss Tedlock,you look lovely today.
泰洛克小姐,你今天真漂亮
That is a very flattering sleeve length on you.
我能说这件衣服真好看吗?
Mr. Costilick would like you to stop by his office today.
科斯特.力克先生希望你在下班后 能到他办公室去
If it's about those prank memos, I wasn't involved.
如果他是为搞笑备忘录 不是我干的,
Nothing at all. Really.
和我完全没有关系.真的.
And frankly,those shenanigans have no place in an office environment.
弗兰克,办公室里没有地方容纳这些恶作剧.
Hey,you guys!
各位,
Chandler's coming and he has incredible news.
钱德说他有天大的好消息
So when he gets here, let's all act,like,you know
所以他来的时候我们就……
Never mind. But it was gonna be really good.
不管了,这一定很有意思.
What's going on?
到底怎么了…
So it's a typical day at work...
今天和平常没什么两样
...and Big Al tells me he wants to make me processing supervisor.
然后艾尔叫我到他办公室 说他要我当电脑处理的主管
-That is great! -Congratulations!
-真是太好了 -恭喜...
So I quit.
所以我就辞职不干了
Why?
为什么?
Why? This was a temp job.
为什么?因为这只是暂时的工作
Chandler,you've been there for five years.
钱德,你已在公司五年了
I know,but if I took it,I'd be admitting that this is what I do.
我知道,但接受升职 不就承认这就是我的目的
Does that mean we have to start buying our own toilet paper?
这是不是意味着我们必须开始自己购买手纸
That was Joey Tribbiani with the big picture. Dan?
那是有大照片的乔伊.丹?
Was it more money?
这那不是能赚更多钱?
Doesn't matter. I just don't want to be a guy who sits in his office...
我不在乎,我不想成为 坐在办公室到午夜
...worrying about the WENUS.
担心"WEENUS"的人
The "WENUS"?
"WENUS"?
Weekly estimated net usage system. It's a processing term.
"每周估计净值使用系统" 这是电脑处理的术语
Oh,that WENUS.
哦，那个是"WENUS"啊
What will you do?
你有何打算?
I don't know. But I won't figure it out working there.
我也不知道该怎么办 我只知道我不会再待在那儿工作了
I have something you can do!
我有一份你可以做的工作
I have this new massage client,Steve.
我的新按摩客户史蒂芬
Anyway,he's opening up a restaurant...
他开了一家餐厅
...and he's looking for a head chef.
他正在寻找总厨师
-Hi,there. -Hi.
-你好 -你好.
I know. You're a chef and I thought of you first.
我知道你是个厨师,而且我先想到你
But Chandler's the one who needs a job right now,so....
但钱德目前没有工作所以...
I just don't have a lot of chef-ing experience.
我没有太多厨师的经验
Unless it's an all-toast restaurant.
除非那是一家只卖土司的餐厅
What is he looking for?
他想要什么菜色?
He wants to do something eclectic.
他想要菜色丰富多变
He's looking for someone who can create the entire menu.
因此他在找一个能创造出整个菜单的人
So,what do you think?
意下如何?
Thanks. I just don't see myself in a big,white hat.
谢了.我大概没资格戴白色大帽吧(无法胜任)
Oh,Monica! Guess what?
摩妮卡,考虑考虑?
a perfect run-up and there he goes,a perfect....
一个完美的积累,然后就自然而然出现了,完美的
Watch stuff like this...
看看这个
...and you realize why evolution is just a theory.
你就知道为什么变革仅仅是理论上的事情了.
Can you see my nipples through this shirt?
你能透过衬衫看见我的乳头吗?
No,but don't worry. I'm sure they're still there.
看不见,但别担心,它们还在
Where are you going?
你要上哪儿去,西装笔挺先生?
I have an appointment with Dr. Robert Pilman,career counselor-a-go-go!
我和罗伯提曼博士有约,求职顾问阿哥哥
-I added the "a-go-go." -Career counselor?
-阿哥哥是我加的 -求职顾问?
You guys all know what you want to do.
你们都已找到人生的方向
I don't.
还没
You guys in the living room all know what you want to do.
在客厅里的各位 全都知道未来该怎么走
You have goals. You have dreams. I don't have a dream!
你们有目标,有梦想, 但我却没有梦想
The lesser-known "I Don't Have a Dream" speech.
少见的“我没有梦想”演说
I love my life! I love my life!
我爱我的人生!我爱我的人生!
"Brian's Song"!
布莱恩的歌
-The meeting went great? -So great!
-见面的结果如何? -相当顺利
He showed me where the restaurant's gonna be.
他告诉我未来餐厅的位置
It's not too big or too small. It's just right.
就在第十街不太大也不太小, 大小适中
Was it formerly owned by a blond woman and some bears?
前任老板是金发女人和几只熊吗?
I'm cooking for him Monday, kind of an audition.
周一我们要煮一餐让他品尝 有点像是面试
Phoebe,he wants you here. It's great. You can make yummy noises.
菲比,他也要你在场 这样对我有好处 因为你可以发出好吃的赞叹声
-What are you gonna make? -Yummy noises.
-你打算做什么? -好吃的声音.
-And Monica,what are you gonna make? -I don't know. It's gotta be great.
摩妮卡,你要做什么菜? 我也不知道,但一定会很棒的
I know what you can make! I know!
我知道你可以做什么了!
You should make that thing with the stuff.
你应该用那些东西做这个.
You know that thing with the stuff?
你知道用那些东西做的这个?
Okay,I don't know.
好吧,我也不知道
Anyone know a good date place in the neighborhood?
各位,谁知道附近有约会的绝佳地点?
How about Tony's? If you finish a 32-ounce steak,it's free.
东尼餐厅如何?吃下32盎斯的牛排就免费
Anyone know a good place if you're not dating a puma?
谁知道和美洲豹约会,哪儿是好地点?
-Who are you going out with? -ls this the bug lady?
-你要和谁约会? -是昆虫女?
"I love you,Ross."
我爱你,罗斯
Her name is Celia and she's insect curator at the museum.
她叫希莉亚,不是昆虫女 她是昆虫博物馆的主任
-What are you gonna do? -Go out to dinner...
-你们打算如何共渡? -出去吃晚餐
...then bring her back to my place and introduce her to my monkey.
然后带她回我的住处 介绍我的猴子给她认识
And he's not speaking metaphorically.
他没用暗示
So back to your place? You thinking maybe....
回你的住处?你想...
Well,I don't know....
我不知道…
I'm hoping....
我希望…
That monkey is a chick magnet.
告诉你,那猴子是魅力十足
She'll take one look at his cute, little face and it'll seal the deal.
她看见它那毛绒绒可爱的小脸 然后一切就搞定
Celia,don't worry. He's not gonna hurt you!
希莉亚,别担心,它不会伤害你的
Soothing tones.
用安抚的语调
-Here,Marcel. -I can't stand this.
-过来,马修 -我受不了了.
-He's got his claws on my -Yeah,all right.
-它的爪子在我的 -乖..
Okay,try this salmon mousse.
试试这鲑鱼慕斯
Good.
好吃
Is it better than the other salmon mousse?
比其他的鲑鱼慕斯好吃?
-It's creamier. -Yeah? Well,is that better?
-更滑更柔 -是吗?这样更好?
I don't know. We're talking about whipped fish.
我不知道.我们在谈一条搅成泡沫的鱼
I'm just happy I'm keeping it down.
我能不吐出来就已经不错了
God,what happened to you?
天啊,你怎么了?
Eight and a half hours of aptitude tests...
8个半小时的性向测验
...intelligence tests,personality tests,and what do I learn?
智力测验,个性测验,我了解了什么?
"You're suited for data processing for a large multinational corporation."
你适合在大型跨国公司 资料处理部门方面发展
That's so great! You already know how to do that.
这太好了 因为你已知道该如何做
Can you believe it?
你们能相信吗?
Don't I seem like I should be doing something cool?
我不像是做那种酷工作的人吗?
I just always pictured myself doing something....
我总是想像自己能做点事情
Something!
事情!
Chandler,I know,I know.
钱德,我知道
Hey,you can see your nipples through this shirt.
嗨,你可以透过你的衬衫 看自己的乳头
Maybe this will cheer you up.
这个或许能让你开心点
I had a grape about five hours ago, so I better split this with you.
5小时前我吃了一颗葡萄 所以我最好该和你平分
It's supposed to be small. It's a pre-appetizer.
它本来就应该那么小 这是餐前开胃菜
The French call it an amuse-bouche.
法国人称它为“阿姆兹布许”
Well,it is amusing.
这简直是太神奇了
Hi,Wendy. Yeah,8:00.
温蒂,对,八点
What did we say,$10 an hour?
我们不是说过吗?每小时十块
Okay,great. All right,I'll see you then.
很好,再见了
-$10 an hour for what? -A waitress from work is helping me.
-什么每小时十块? -我请餐厅里的女服务生帮忙
Waitressing?
服务生?
Of course I thought of you. But....
当然我考虑过你.但...
-But.... -But,but....
-但是… -但是什么?
But it's just this night has to go just perfect,you know?
但是这今晚一定要做到完美,你知道吗?
Wendy's more of a professional waitress.
温蒂的经验丰富,是个职业服务生
And I'm maintaining my amateur status so I can waitress in the Olympics.
我应该继续保持业余的姿态 将来才能在奥运会上当服务生
I don't mean to brag,but I waited tables at lnnsbruck in '76.
我不想自吹自擂 但我在76年的因斯布鲁克当过服务生
Took home a bronze.
带回家一块铜牌.
Amuse-bouche?
阿姆兹-布许?
Talk to me.
和我说话
A weird thing happened on the train this morning
早上我坐地铁时 发生了一件诡异的事
Talk dirty.
说猥亵的话
-Here? -Come on. Come on.
-这里? -对.
Say something hot.
说点火辣的
What? What?
什么?什么?
Vulva.
外阴.
Vulva?
外阴?
I panicked,all right? She took me by surprise.
我当时好害怕,她吓了我一跳
But it wasn't a total loss. We ended up cuddling.
但并未完全失去自我.我们以爱抚收场
You cuddled? How many times?
爱抚?几次?
Shut up. It was nice.
闭嘴,那种感觉好好
I don't think I'm a dirty-talking kind of guy.
我不是那种讲猥亵话的人
Just say what you wanna do to her. Or what you want her to do to you.
你只要说出你想对她如何 或是你想她对你如何
Or what other people might be doing to each other.
或是别人想对彼此如何
I'll tell you what. Try something on me.
这样吧,对我说吧
Please be kidding.
开什么玩笑
Why not?
有何不可,
Just close your eyes and tell me what you'd like to be doing right now.
只要闭上眼睛告诉我 现在你想干什么
I'm in my apartment....
好吧…我在我的住处
-Yeah,what else? -You're not there.
-然后呢? -你不在那里.
-We're not having this conversation. -All right,I'll start. Ready?
-我们在进行这样的谈话 -好的,我要开始了,准备好了吗?
Oh,Ross...
噢,罗斯
...you get me so hot. I want your lips on me now.
你让我欲火焚身, 我要你舔我
-Now you say something. -I really don't think so.
-该你了 -我看还是算了吧
You like this woman,right? You wanna see her again,right?
你喜欢她吧?想再见到她吗?
If you can't talk dirty to me, how will you talk dirty to her?
如果你无法对我说出狠亵的话 你如何对她说呢?
Now tell me you wanna caress my butt!
说你想爱抚我的屁股
Okay,turn around.
好吧,转过去
I don't want you staring at me.
我不想你盯著我看
All right,I'm not looking. Go ahead.
好吧,我不看,说吧
Okay.
Ok.
I want Okay,I want...
我要...
...to feel your hot,soft skin with my lips.
用我的双唇感觉你那光滑的皮肤
There you go. IKeep going,keep going.
这就对了,继续
I want to take my tongue and
我要用我的舌头…
Say it.
快说啊
Say it!
快说
run it all over your body...
舔遍你的全身
... until you're trembling with
直到你颤抖…
With?
然后呢?
-Funny story. -You're not gonna believe this.
-真好笑 -你不会相信的
I was always rooting for you two kids to get together.
我一向赞成你们两个小子交往
-The trembling thing was nice. -Shut up!
-颤抖那一段不错 -闭嘴!
That guy from your old job called again.
你睡觉时老东家又打电话来
-Again? -And again and again and again.
-又打来? -一遍又一遍.
And again.
又打来了
Hey,Mr. Costilick. How's life on the 1 5th floor?
科先生,15楼的情况如何?
Yeah,I miss you too.
我也想念你.
It's a lot less satisfying to steal pens from your own home.
对,偷家里的笔不够刺激
That's very generous. But this isn't about the money.
你真慷慨,但这不是钱的问题
I need more than a job. I need something I really care ab
我需要的不只是一份工作 我要的是我真正想要的
That's on top of the year-end bonus?
这是你稍早提过的年终红利之外的津贴?
Your dream!
你的梦想…
Look,Al,I'm not playing hardball here,okay?
艾尔,我不是在故意为难你
This is not a negotiation. This is a rejection!
这不是交涉,这叫拒绝
Stop saying numbers!
不,别再讲数字了
I'm telling you, you've got the wrong guy!
告诉你,你看错人了
I'll see you Monday!
星期一见
Wow! It's huge! It's so much bigger than the cubicle.
好大,比小格子大多了
This is a cube!
这是一个格间!
Look at this.
看这里.
You have a window!
你有窗户!
Yes,indeed-y. With a beautiful view of
没错,还有美丽的风…
Look! That guy's peeing!
看,有人在小便
That's enough of the view. Check this out.
风景看够了,看这个
Okay,sit down here.
坐下
This is great.
这个最酷,
-You ready? -Yeah.
-准备好没? -好了
Helen,could you come in here?
海伦,能进来一下吗?
Thank you,Helen. That'll be all.
谢谢你,海伦,没事了
Last time I do that. I promise.
最后一次了,我保证
-She doesn't seem very warm. -I know. She has no personality.
-她看起来不怎么热情 -我知道.她没有个性.
Wendy,don't do this to me.
温蒂,不要这样对我.
We had a deal. Yeah,you promised.
我们约好的.你答应过我
-Who was that? -Wendy bailed.
-那是谁? -叛徒温蒂
I have no waitress.
我没服务生了
That's too bad. Bye-bye.
真是太糟糕了.再见
Ten dollars an hour! Twelve dollars an hour!
一小时十元!一小时十二元!
I wish I could,but I've made plans to walk around.
我希望可以 但我已经计划好去走走
When you ran out on your wedding, I was there.
你逃婚之后我一直关心你
I put a roof over your head! If that means nothing....
我让你有地方住 如果这样对你仍毫无意义…
Twenty dollars an hour.
一小时二十元
Done.
成交
Hello. Welcome to Monica's. May I take your coat?
欢迎光临摩尼卡的厨房 我能拿你的外套吗?
-Hi,Steve. -Hello,Monica.
-史帝夫 -摩妮卡
Hello,greeter girl.
招待小姐
-This is Rachel. -Yeah,okay.
-她叫瑞秋 -好的,
Everything smells so delicious.
味道好香
I can't remember ever smelling such a delicious combination of
我早已忘记这种…
Okay,smells.
香味
-It's a lovely apartment. -Thank you. Would you like a tour?
-这房子真漂亮 -谢谢,想参观一下吗?
I was just being polite, but all right.
我只是客套一下,但,好吧
-What's up? -ln the cab on the way over...
-怎么了? -他坐计程车来时
...Steve blazed up a doobie.
燃了一根草
What?
什么?
Smoked a joint,you know? Lit a bone. Weed,hemp,ganja
抽了一根大麻… 好了,我懂
I'm with you,Cheech.
我和你在一起,cheech.
-Do you think he's gonna be cool? -ls it dry in here?
-你认为他会冷静吗? -这里很干燥吗?
Let me get you some wine.
我来为你倒杯酒
I think we're ready for our first course too.
我们可以上第一道菜了
These are rock shrimp ravioli in a cilantro ponzu sauce...
这些是石虾小方饺
...with just a touch of minced...
芫萎调味酱加上一点点…
...ginger.
碎姜
Well,smack my ass and call me Judy!
打我屁股叫我朱蒂
-These are fantastic! -Gosh! I'm so glad you liked them.
-真是太好吃了 -我真高兴你喜欢
Like them? I could eat 100 of them!
喜欢?我可以吃下上百个
That's all there is of these...
只有这一些
...but in a few minutes, we'll serve some tartlets.
但再过8分半钟 我们就会献上美味的洋葱馅饼
"Tartlets"?
馅饼...
"Tartlets."
Word has lost all meaning.
文字都已失去意义
Excuse me. Can I help you with anything?
请问需要任何帮忙吗?
You know,I don't know what I'm looking for.
你看,我也不知道自己在找什么
Cool! Taco shells!
酷,墨西哥馅饼
They're like a little corn envelope,you know?
这个就像是玉米卷
-You don't wanna spoil your appetite. -Hey,Sugar-O's!
-你不该影响食欲. -糖欧
You know,if you just wait another 6 1 /2 minutes
再等6分钟半
Macaroni and cheese! We gotta make this!
乾酪通心面!我们要做这个
-No,we don't. -Oh,okay.
-不,我们不做 -哦,好吧.
Sorry.
抱歉
Why don't you just have a seat here?
我们何不坐这儿
-Give me the gummy bears. -No.
-小熊软糖给我 -不
-Give them to me. -We'll share.
-把他给我 -好吧,分你一半
-No. Give me the bears. -You can't have any.
-小熊给我 -你不能全部抢走
It's not worth it!
这样不值得!
Bears overboard! They're drowning!
小熊落水了,他们快淹死了
Don't just stand there. Call 9-1 -1.
不要站在那里.打9-1-1.
Hey,fellas,grab onto a Sugar-O! Save yourselves!
嗨,伙计们,抓住糖欧逃命啊!
Help! Help,I'm drowning!
救命啊....我淹水了
-That's it! Dinner is over! -What! Why?
-我受够了,晚餐结束 -什么?为什么?
Why? What if I came into your office and I started...?
什么?试想一下我到你的办公室然后开始...?
I can't think of an example.
我想不出一个合适的例子.
I've waited seven years for an opportunity like this...
这机会我已等了七年
...and you can't wait 4 1 /2 minutes for a tartlet?
而你却等不了四分半钟之后 再吃洋葱馅饼
So I told him, "I'm sorry. That's how I feel."
所以我跟他说, "对不起.这就是我的感受."
And he told me I harsh-ed his buzz.
他居然说我声音太刺耳搞得他耳朵嗡嗡叫
Then I said,"Don't eat that. It's a kitchen magnet."
然后我说,"别吃这个,这是厨房磁铁"
And he didn't listen, so we left him in the emergency room.
结果他不听,我们只好把他留在急救室了.
-Mon,I'm sorry. -What a tool.
-摩尼卡,对不起 -真是个王八蛋
-You did the right thing. -You don't wanna work for that guy.
-你做的很对 -你不会想为那种人工作的
I just thought that this was it.
我以为我的机会来了
-Don't worry. You're an amazing chef. -Those yummy noises? I wasn't faking.
-不要担心.你是个了不起的厨师 -记得那些赞美的声音?我不是装的
Am I gonna get paid for the full three hours?
我能拿到全时三小时工资吗?
Just a question. We'll talk about it later.
只是一个问题而已.我们以后再说.
So,how did it go with Celia?
和希莉亚的状况如何?
-I was unbelievable. -All right,Ross!
-我简直是太神了 -干得好,罗斯!
I was the James Michener of dirty talk.
我就像是詹姆斯密奇尼一样满口狠亵的话
It was the most elaborate filth ever heard.
天下最具巧思的猥亵话
I mean,there were characters, plot lines,themes,a motif.
有人物,剧情,主题
At one point,there were villagers.
其中一段的主角是村夫与村姑
And?
然后呢?
By the time we finished all the dirty talk...
猥亵话讲完后已经很晚了
...it was late and we were exhausted
而且我们也已精疲力竭所以…
-You cuddled. -Yeah,which was nice.
-你们爱抚? -那种感觉好好
Do you guys want to try to catch a late movie?
你们想看晚场电影吗?
-Shouldn't we wait for Chandler? -Where the hell is he?
-或许吧,但我们不是该等钱德? -他到底跑哪儿去了?
I know what time it is...
我知道现在几点
...but I'm looking at the WENUS and I'm not happy!
但我看着WENUS而且我相当不高兴
Let me tell you something.
真的?告诉你吧
You will care about it because I care about it. Got it? Good!
你会在乎是因为我在乎,明白了吗?很好!
How's this?
这样如何?
Sorry. How about over here?
不好意思,这边那?
That means it's working.
这就说明有效果了.
-Does this hurt? -No.
-痛不痛? -不痛.
How about this?
这样呢?
There you go!
爽啦!
I'm gonna throw up!
爽呆了!!